http://www.mcginnislaw.com/legal/privacy

Telecommunications
Unmanned Aircraft Systems (UAS)
South Texas
Unmanned Aircraft Systems (UAS)
Technology
Unmanned Aircraft Systems (UAS)
Telecommunications
Unmanned Aircraft Systems (UAS)
About Us
For 90 years, McGinnis Lochridge has served to protect the interests of our clients in continuously changing landscapes including cutting-edge technology, oil and gas litigation, regulatory matters and more. The quality of our work is reflected in our clients’ long-lasting loyalty and in our top-tier external rankings.
About Our Firm
History
SCG Legal
Diversity Commitment
Charitable/Civic
Pro Bono
Careers
Notable Past Members
Generations of Leadership
Firm Founders
Locations
Contact
Privacy Policy
Legal › Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us.  This privacy statement (“Privacy Statement”) explains how we may collect, store and use the information you provide to us using this website and any other website, application or other service on which this Privacy Statement appears (collectively, the “Website”), and does not apply to any of our other practices and activities. The term “you” refers to you individually and, if applicable, your employer.  The term “we” or “us” refers to McGinnis, Lochridge & Kilgore, L.L.P.
Information We Collect While You Are Browsing the Website
Browsing Information Generally
We do not collect personally-identifiable information when you browse the Website and request pages from our servers unless you voluntarily and knowingly provide it to us.  This means that we will not know your name, your email address, or any other personally-identifiable information just because you browse the Website unless you:
access the Website from a link in an email that we sent;
you have created an account to access certain features of the Website and log in to your account; or
you otherwise voluntary provide us this information by typing it into fields provided on this Website.
When you request a page from the Website, we may automatically collect and store: the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet; the Internet protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using; the browser software you use and your operating system; the date and time you access our sites; and the Internet address of the site from which you linked directly to our sites.
Cookies and Pixel Tags
The Website uses “cookies,” which are encrypted strings of text that a Website stores on a user’s computer.  The Website may require the use of a cookie to provide certain features or functionality.  Without cookies we will not be able to keep information you enter on multiple pages together.  For example, unless the Website can remember specific features you may be looking for in a community, the Website will not be able to make suggestions that may be of interest to you.  Cookies also enable us to customize the Website and offerings to your needs and provide you with a better online experience.
The types of cookies that we use are referred to as “session” cookies and “persistent” cookies.  Session cookies are temporary and are automatically deleted once you close your Internet browser.  Persistent cookies remain on your computer hard drive until you delete them or are otherwise removed upon expiration.  We do not use cookies to ascertain any personally-identifiable information about you apart from what you voluntarily provide us.
You may set your browser to block cookies (consult the instructions for your particular browser on how to do this), although doing so will adversely affect your ability to use certain functionality and access certain content on the Website.
We and our third-party service providers may use “pixel tags” (also known as “clear gifs,” “beacon gifs,” etc.).  Pixel tags are not visible to the user of a website and consist of a few lines of computer coding delivered with the web page.  Pixel tags are not used to collect any personally identifiable information about you apart from what you voluntarily provide us.
Contact and other Information About You
We may offer web-based tools allowing you, at your choice, to create an account to access certain features of the Website or to send a communication to us via the Website or via electronic mail.  As a result of such activities:
Contact Information.  You may choose to provide us with your name, preferred user name, email address, telephone number and street address.
Information about You.  You may choose to provide us with information about your personal preferences, such as newsletters you would like to receive.
Other Unsolicited Information.  NOTICE:  Although we would like to hear from you, we cannot represent you until we know that doing so will not create a conflict of interest.  Also, we cannot treat unsolicited information as confidential.  Accordingly, please do not send us any information about any matter that may involve you until you receive a written statement from us that we represent you (an “engagement letter”).
To initiate a possible representation, you should call one of our attorneys at the telephone number specified on the Website.  He or she will determine if any conflict exists, and, if not, put you in touch with an appropriate lawyer.
When you receive an engagement letter from that lawyer, you will be our client, and we may exchange information freely.
By initiating communications with us through the Website (whether by clicking a button labeled "OK," “ACCEPT,” “I AGREE,” “EMAIL US” or otherwise), you agree that we may review any information you transmit to us.  You recognize that our review of your information prior to the establishment of an attorney-client relationship, even if you submitted it in a good faith effort to retain us, and even if you consider it confidential, does not preclude us from representing another client directly adverse to you, even in a matter where the information could and will be used against you.
How We Use Your Information
Browsing Information, Cookies and Pixel Tags
We use general browsing information to determine the number of visitors to different sections of our sites, to ensure the sites are working properly, and to help us make our sites more useful.  We may also use this information to personalize content presented to you, and to better understand how visitors use the Website and how we can better tune it, its contents, and functionality to meet your needs.
We may use cookies to (a) measure usage of various pages on our Website to help us make our information more pertinent to your needs and easy for you to access, (b) provide additional functionality such as commenting and provision of suggestions that we believe would be of interest and value to you, and (c) to enhance your use of the Website.
We and our third-party service providers may use pixel tags to improve customer service, learn how visitors use our Website, know how many users open an email and allow our service provider to compile aggregated statistics about an email campaign for us.
Contact and other Information
If you provide us with contact information or any other information about yourself (such as feature preferences), we may use that information in the following ways:
to send you a variety of administrative communications, such as notifying you about your account or account activity, or to send you other information about our relationship with you;
to respond to requests, including requests for additional information about our products or services;
to improve our products and services and for any other business purposes;
to analyze, improve, customize or make other changes to the Website;
to protect the Website and its users, and us and our affiliates, as we deem necessary; and
To send periodic emails - We may use your email address to respond to your inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you may receive emails that include our news, updates, or related information. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you may do so using the procedures described below or at the bottom of our email to you.
Opting Out of Communications
If you have an account on the Website, we will provide you the ability to define and modify your email and mailing preferences online at any time including unsubscribing from all marketing communications.
When you receive an email, you may be provided the choice to opt out of future emails by following the instructions provided in the email.
You may also opt out of receiving marketing communications by making an opt-out request in any of the following ways:
sending us an email to info@mcginnislaw.com;
sending us a letter at 600 Congress Avenue, Suite 2100, Austin, Texas 78701; or
calling us at (512) 495-6000.
Please allow 15 business days for us to process any opt-out request.
How We Share Your Information with Third Parties
We may use the services of third parties to assist us in operating or improving the Website, including web hosting and email service providers and they may have access to your personally identifiable information you submit to us.  These parties are contractually prohibited from using personally-identifiable information for any purpose other than for the purpose we specify.  We may provide non-personally identifiable information to certain service providers for their use on an aggregated basis for the purpose of performing their contractual obligations to us.
We may provide your information to a party that is interested in acquiring, or does acquire, all or a portion of our business.  We also may provide your information in response to a request from a court, law enforcement agency or other government agency.
We do not permit the sale or transfer of personally-identifiable information to entities outside of our affiliates and our third-party service providers for any use unrelated to our relationship with you without your approval.
Use of Log-in Information
You are required to protect the confidentiality of any password or user ID we provide to you.  You should also log off or close your browser after you visit any secure areas of our site in order to help protect against unauthorized access by third parties.  You are responsible for any use of the Website under your password or user ID, regardless of whether such use was authorized.
Security
We maintain reasonable security procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online or store electronically.  We may hire third parties to store and manage data provided they observe the same or equivalent security and privacy guidelines.  However, because of the inherent risks associated with the Internet, we cannot provide a 100% guarantee of data security.  In the event of a security breach, we will comply with legal requirements regarding notice of that breach, but you agree that we will not have any other liability other than providing the required notice.  If you do not agree to this waiver, you should not provide personally-identifiable information to us.
Commitment to Children’s Privacy
Protecting the privacy of children is especially important to us.  For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at the Website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of the Website is structured to attract anyone under the age of 13.  It is our policy to comply in all respects with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA).
Other Sites
We are responsible only for the Privacy Statement and content of this Website.  We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the use of cookies on websites that you have accessed this Website from and to any unaffiliated websites that you may access from this Website, including any websites to which we provide links.
Legal Issues
This is a United States website and is subject to laws of the United States and the State of Texas.
If you reside in the State of California, you have the right to request from us a list of third parties with whom we shared personally-identifiable information about you for their own direct marketing purposes during the previous calendar year.  We do not share personally-identifiable information with third parties for their own direct marketing purposes.
Phishing Warning
We will never request your credit card number or social security number.  Please also note that we will never send you email requesting your user name, password, credit card number or social security number.  If you receive an email that looks like it is from us, but asks you for your credit card number or social security number, it is a fraudulent or “phishing” email.  We recommend that you forward the email to the Federal Trade Commission at spam@uce.gov to report it, and then delete it.  The Federal Trade Commission uses the spam forwarded to it to investigate and pursue law enforcement actions against people who send deceptive email.
If you believe “phishers” have gotten access to your personal or financial information, we recommend that you also change your password on any account you may have with us.
Please be aware that the perpetrator may attempt to use your information to establish accounts or obtain credit at other businesses in their name.  We are not responsible for the actions of “phishers” even though the email may appear to have been sent by us.
Comments or Feedback
If you have comments or would like to provide feedback to this Privacy Statement, please contact us by sending an email to info@mcginnislaw.com or a letter to 600 Congress Avenue, Suite 2100, Austin, Texas 78701.
Changes to this Privacy Statement
In the future, we may need to change this Privacy Statement.  All changes will be shown here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone.  If we change our Privacy Statement in a manner that expands our rights to use or disclose your data, we will send you notice by email with a description of the change.  You will have an opportunity to reject that change by using the opt-out procedures described above or in that email.  Our goal is to provide you at least thirty (30) days notice before the change is effective, but that may not always be possible.  If you do not opt out, the amendment may be retroactive to information you previously supplied.  If we change our Privacy Statement in a manner that does not expand our rights to use or disclose your data (i.e. to update the policy to address new legislation or to change references to names or marks), then we may post the new Privacy Statement without sending an email to you.  That new policy will take effect once it is posted on this Website.
This statement was last updated on August 1, 2013.
600 Congress Ave., Ste. 2100, Austin,TX 78701 | 512 495-6000 p | 512 495-6093 f
